when you apply for a participating
policy or universal life insurance the
insurance company will invest the
premiums paid by you and other policy
holders therefore in addition to
considering the reputation of the
insurance company its investment
capability is also very important our
investment capabilities are at the
center of delivering what matters most
to our customers that is to seek stable
long-term risk adjusted return for
manual life's Affiliates and their
customers during the life of their
policies manae manages $311 billion US
assets for its Insurance businesses
globally with Investments spanning North
America Latin America Europe Asia
Pacific and the Middle East we focus on
the development of the insurance
business in Asia the total value of our
investment assets has doubled since 2013
in our Diversified portfolio in addition
to traditional listed public bonds and
equities we also look for high quality
opportunities in alternative Assets in
private markets private assets often
have lower volatility than their public
counterparts offering diversification
benefits and less correlated returns
providing sustainable and stable
long-term returns investing in private
debt helps our fixed income portfolio by
enhancing yield and diversifying risk
manual life has more than a 100
investment professionals specialized by
industry to support our investment we
have been a leading participant in the
US market for more than 30 years and we
are one of the largest private placement
Securities participants in Canada of the
debt Securities in private placement
debt 96% are investment
grade all our assets are directly
managed by manual life group and its
Affiliates this helps us keep up to- dat
on what we invest in and invest only in
what we truly understand we have
specialized sector teams that cover all
range of disciplines to support our
investments including financials natural
resources consumer Industrials
Technology power and infrastructure
Etc in 2022 manual life made a strategic
Bond investment in a large Water
Utilities company in Chile this
transaction was granted in ESG Bond
designation and proceeds were directed
towards enhancing drinking water supply
building resilient infrastructure and
advancing wastewater treatment through
private equity and infrastructure
investment ments we capture
opportunities that are not traded in the
public markets but have strong growth
and income potential manual life invest
in financially and operationally sound
companies and infrastructure assets both
directly and through our investments in
private equity and infrastructure funds
our investments are Diversified across
geographies fund managers and investment
strategies notable emerging Industries
we invested in include 5G infrastructure
renewable energy fintech health
healthare Services just to name a few in
2017 Mana lifee completed an equity
co-investment in an international
schools organization further expanding
our investment activity in the resilient
education sector globally manual life is
also an active participant in global
real estate investment projects for its
Insurance businesses we manage a global
portfolio invested in Diversified types
of properties including offices
industrial multif family retail land and
development in Asia Pacific our property
Investments are spread across the region
recent Milestones include the forward
purchase of an office building in
Australia Logistics portfolios or
forward purchases in Australia Vietnam
and South Korea as well as CORE multif
family projects and forward purchases in
Japan in 2015 we took the lead in Hong
Kong to acquire a 21-story great a
commercial building now known as Mano
life tower our early entry into East Kon
made us a Pioneer in this new Corp
business district historically farmlands
have had a low correlation with the
performance of more traditional asset
classes in 2017 we acquired
approximately 1,800 hectares of Farmland
in South Australia operating as a
highquality almond Orchard in 2018 we
acquired a 5,000 1888 gross hectare Farm
in Queensland Australia with a primary
crop of cotton and winter crops of Wheat
and barley stability and diversification
benefits make Timberland an appealing
option into the portfolio in 2023 manual
life in Asia made its first investment
in Timberland in Australia contributing
to the diversity of our investment mix
in the region this transaction
represents the first Timberland
investment made by an insurer in Asia
ESG is also an integral part of our
investment strategy reflecting our
commitment to promoting green and
sustainable Investments we aim to reduce
absolute scope 1 and two emissions by
40% by 2035 and reach our Net Zero
commitment by
2050 we are also committed to creating
products that solve policy holders needs
and contribute to a sustainable future
our portfolio of sustainable Investments
has increased by 75% compared to 2019
totaling 48.3 billion as at December
31st
2023 to name a few of our recent
transactions in Asia we are a lead
investor in cambodia's first sustainable
Bond issued by the only Cambodian
homegrown mobile network operator we
also invested in sustainable Asia Bond
assets through an article 9
fund manual life has a pragmatic
financial and risk management investment
philosophy that keeps Pace with the
times as well as strong and experienced
Investment Management teams we manage a
diversified and high-quality Investment
Portfolio
that is well positioned to provide
policy holders with protection and peace
of mind